(Penny:)Oh, hey, I was
just on my way to work.
(Leonard:)Oh, okay,
its not important.
(Leonard:)It can wait.
(Penny:)No, it's all right.
Walk me down.
(Leonard:)So, what's up?
(Leonard:)Uh, I kind of have
a problem
(Leonard:)I was hoping
you could help me with.
(Penny:)Sure, anything.
(Leonard:)Move out.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Not far.
(Leonard:)Hey, if you ever wanna
start a family,
La Cañada has
some great schools.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm not
moving anywhere.
(Penny:)What the hell
is this all about?
(Leonard:)Why does it have
to be about anything?
(Leonard:)Can't a fella ask
his buddy to relocate,
(Leonard:)no questions asked?
(Penny:)Oh, for God's sake,
Leonard,
(Penny:)this is about Priya,
isn't it?
(Penny:)She doesn't want me
hanging out with you.
(Leonard:)Yes. There, I said it.
(Penny:)Okay, look.
(Penny:)I happen to like
your girlfriend.
(Leonard:)And she likes you.
(Penny:)No, she doesn't.
(Leonard:)Not really, no.
(Penny:)It doesn't matter.
Look, I promise from now on
(Penny:)I will keep
my distance from you.
(Leonard:)Well, now, hold on.
What kind of distance
(Leonard:)are we talking about?
Because we are neighbors.
(Leonard:)I mean, I can hear the toilet
flush in your apartment.
(Penny:)You can hear my toilet flush?